Episode 4    Could You Please Tell Me Why?
Hey, Desumi!
Walk home with us!
Sure!
Allow me to explain!
Reaper Princess, A.K.A. Desumi Magahara,
is a teenage girl who hides
her villainous identity
to attend high school in the city!
Don't you have handicrafts club today, Desumi?
It's off for test prep today.
Wanna go for some karaoke, then?
Sorry, I have work today.
What, again?
You're a real workaholic, Desumi.
You'll never get a boyfriend that way!
A boyfriend...
Oh, a boyfriend...
We'll see, I guess!
Where's this coming from?
Hey, you got a crush on someone?
Not telling!
Hey, it's Red Gelato!
Fudo!
F-Fudo?
Fudo?
Shock
Fudo?!
I-Isn't that...
Is that their new Pink he's with?
It is! She's so cute!
You think they're dating or something?
They totally might be!
They look really good together.
Totally! A real perfect couple!
Right, Desumi?
What's with the face?!
Huh? Desumi!
Desumi?
You rarely invite me out like this, Haru-kun.
I'm s-sorry, Fudo-senpai.
I know you're really busy...
Hey, not a problem.
So, what was it you wanted to ask me about?
W-Well...
It is rude to ask about this, isn't it?
But I just can't stop
thinking about that photo!
Was that really Fudo-senpai?
If it was, that girl next to him...
Could she be... his girlfriend?
But is it really okay for me
to ask about his private life?!
I understand.
I think I know what you want to ask about.
Huh?
For Those Seeking
Muscle Growth
Rules for
High-Efficiency
Training
By Fudo Aikawa
Refreshing!
Goes down easy!
I think this should take care of it!
Um...
For Those Seeking
Muscle Growth
Rules for
High-Efficiency
Training
Refreshing!
Goes down easy!
What's this stuff?
You've been with the squad
about six months now, right?
Y-Yes...
You'll be hitting a wall with your
strength training around now.
What?
It's nothing to worry about.
The same thing happened to me.
What?
Follow this training regimen
over the next six months,
and you'll obtain a body
of steel that will get you
through just about any battle situation!
W-Wait a minute, Senpai!
What I'm actually concerned
about is the picture—
You're such a worrywart.
Don't worry!
The book does use pictures to explain
the regimen's trickiest parts!
And this kind of incremental
strength training
is specially designed to minimize strain.
It should be easy to follow,
even for someone as small as you.
Since training that harms your
body defeats the point, right?
It's also important to do appropriate
stretches before each lift.
The graphs about that here
should be easy to follow.
That will help increase the
flexibility of your muscles,
and even promote swift
recovery from injuries!
I'm not claiming you'll
see results overnight,
Now I know for certain...
but anyone can get the body they want
with sufficient application of effort.
Senpai does not have a girlfriend!
No need to worry.
When you make the call of effort,
your muscles always answer!
That should cover it.
That's what you wanted to ask, right?
Oh, yes!
Thank you so much!
I'm sorry for doubting you, Senpai!
They're calling us in!
Let's go, Fudo-senpai!
Don't forget your book, Haru-kun!
Here we go!
Culverin Cannon!
That's quite enough of that, Gekko!
Freezing Sentai Gelato 5 has arrived!
Underestimate us on pain of fire!
It's about time, Gelato 5!
Today's the day I take you off the field!
Get them!
Let's go!
Right!
All right, Desumi-san!
What will we chat about to—
Red!
Whoops. Guess my timing's a little off today.
It's okay. It happens.
Let's coordinate our movements, Desumi-sa—
I'll dodge your first strike, then leap back.
Ignored
Ignored...
That hurt!
Desumi-san?
Desu...
L-Let's move this elsewhere, Reaper Princess!
No!
Take this...
Reaper Whirlwind!
Reaper Whirlwind
I... I've never seen this move before!
Desumi-san!
See? You shouldn't use moves you
haven't practiced thoroughly.
H-Hold on, Desumi-san!
What happened to you?
Tell me what's going on!
I saw you two in the café!
I-It's not like that, Desumi-san!
You've got it all wrong!
I was teaching Pink about bodybuilding—
I know that!
I know better than anybody
that you'd never cheat on me.
And yet, seeing the two of you together
sparked this hideous jealousy inside me.
I found myself thinking,
maybe you don't belong
with an outcast like me...
But with a girly girl like her!
That isn't true!
You're the girliest girl I know!
Am not!
I never used to be the kind of person
to worry about that sort of thing!
Love has made me weak!
Dating you has made me...
A weak and pathetic mess of a woman!
That isn't true, Desumi-san!
Fudo...
The person I am...
Maybe I'm just not...
cut out for love.
I'm a pretty awkward guy.
But once I make up my mind about something,
I see it through to the end.
I will love you, and no one else,
for the rest of my life.
Will you trust me, and join me in that?
Yes, I trust you.
That was rough.
Why are you laughing all of a sudden?
I've seen an all-new side of you.
You can be surprisingly negative sometimes!
Snap
Fudo, I still haven't forgiven you
for going on that afterschool date.
W-Well, that wasn't exactly a date.
It was just...
Promise me you'll take me on
an afterschool date, too.
Uniforms and all.
Then I'll forgive you!
I will! I promise I will!
Excuse me.
It's all over, Senpai.
Allow me to explain!
These two are busted!
Love After World Domination!
The
Next
Day
Oh, w-well...
This is just...
Come on.
Let's head back, Senpai.
R-Right...
That's strange.
She hasn't said anything.
Is it possible she hasn't figured us out?
B-By the way, Haru-kun...
How much of our conversation did you hear?
After, "See? You shouldn't use moves
you haven't practiced thoroughly..."
Or thereabouts.
Ah.
So, basically all of it.
It's over.
The End of Justice
Reaper Princess  Steamy Affair  Red
How could you have done this, Fudo-kun?!
The End of Justice
Reaper Princess   Steamy Affair   Red
Utterly unbelievable!
How do you intend to atone for this?
I'm so disappointed, Fudo!
How could you have done this, Fudo-kun?!
Utterly unbelievable!
How do you intend to atone for this?
I'm so disappointed, Fudo!
If that's the situation
that awaits me in there...
What will I do?
What are you doing, Senpai?
The meeting is about to start.
R-Right.
Good morning, Fudo-kun, Haru-kun.
Hey there!
Haru-kun would like to begin the
meeting with an announcement.
Yes.
It's about me and Fudo-senpai.
It's all...
Our end-of-term tests
are starting this week,
so we'll need to leave early.
...not over!
Tests? Boy, that takes me back!
Take care of yourselves.
Why?
Why did she do it?
Why...
Why indeed?
Why hasn't she said anything?!
What in the world is going on?
I don't know, either.
Haru-kun has been acting
normal for the past week,
both at work and at school.
What are you scheming, Pink Gelato?!
I'll bet she's watching us as we speak!
It's all right. That's why
we're keeping our distance.
Oh, it's just a civet.
This is torture! I'm at the end of my rope!
If she insists on forcing my hand...
I'll have to silence her forever!
H-Hang on!
Hold it, Desumi-san!
No need to worry. I won't fail.
T-That isn't what I mean!
I'm sure Haru-kun has her
own reasons for this.
Let's wait and watch a little while longer.
Fudo...
Would you mind buying me a drink?
I'd like a vanilla mocha, with nonfat milk,
extra whip, and almonds.
Vanilla mocha, nonfat milk...
Hang on a minute!
Let me write it down.
Vanilla mocha, nonfat milk,
extra whip, with almonds.
R-Right. On my way.
Thanks.
Shown yourself at last, have you?
There must be a reason why you're not
telling anybody about our relationship.
Would you mind telling me what it is?
Fight me!
Uh?
That's what I want!
You'll accept my challenge,
won't you, Reaper Princess?!
No...
Second-year at Kokutei High School,
Desumi Magahara!
H-How do you know about me?
Here I come!
Change, Gelato!
Her fighting technique has a long way to go.
That's right. She hasn't been
on the team very long.
Can we stop this now?
Not yet...
I'm not finished yet!
Why is she so desperate to...
I'm glad you're awake.
You should probably lay
still a while longer.
I lost.
You really are strong, Desumi-san.
Please tell me. What are you after?
The reason I joined the team
was because I was in love with Fudo-senpai.
That's why I started to
suspect he had a girlfriend.
But I never dreamed his girlfriend
would be an enemy commander.
I see.
It's no wonder she hates me.
But she also happened to be someone I knew.
Huh?
She was...
on that night, when I was attacked by thugs...
the one who saved me.
Become strong.
The person who saved me,
and said those words to me.
That was you?!
I never dreamed you'd turn out
to be the Reaper Princess, either.
To be honest... I thought that if falling
in love really had made you weak,
then maybe I could steal him from you.
But...
But you're as strong as you ever were.
W-Why?
You could have destroyed our
relationship without any of this!
I saw Fudo-senpai smiling in
a way I've never seen before.
So I just can't do it.
I don't have the right to
steal happiness from the two of you.
H-Hey...
Why?
Why are you crying, too?
I'm sorry, Desumi-san.
I can find any of that vanilla almond
thing you were talking about.
Haru-kun?
What the...
Shh...
Pink Gelato came by.
She's sleeping now.
Pale
Did you silence her forever?!
I'm rooting for you two, okay?
But if you give me the chance,
I might just take him from you!
So, you'd better get along!
I know. We will.
See you!
I am a civet.
This is the preview.
Next Time: "Just the Way You Are."
Episode 5     Just the Way You Are
Why a civet?!